A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986, RG 37 FA1504
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986; 37; 327.55 Cubic Feet 857 containers
  - Education, 1982-1986; 12; 40.62 Cubic Feet 102 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes
    - Education - A-Z, 1
      - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars - Kennan Institute for Advanced Russian Studies (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Worldwatch Institute (Box 233, Folder 2-3)
    - Colleges, 2
      - Colleges - A (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - Colleges - B-G (Box 234, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges - H-M (Box 235, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges - N-S (Box 236, Folder 1-4)
      - Colleges - S-Z (Box 237, Folder 1-4)
      - Alfred University (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - American College of Orgonomy (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - American Schools of Oriental Research (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Bard College (Box 238, Folder 4-5)
      - Beirut University College (Box 238, Folder 6)
      - Boston College (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Boston University, Boston, MA (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Boston University, Providence, RI (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Brown University - Center for Foreign Policy Development (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Brandeis University (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Carnegie-Mellon University (Box 239, Folder 6)
      - Cambridge College (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Catholic University of America (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - City University of New York (CUNY) (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - City University of New York (CUNY) - Fiorello H. Laguardia Community College (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - City University of New York (CUNY) - Queens College (Box 241, Folder 2-3)
      - Clark University (Box 242, Folder 1)
      - College of the Atlantic (Box 242, Folder 2)
      - College of the Virgin Islands (Box 242, Folder 3-4)
      - Columbia University (Box 242, Folder 5)
      - Columbia University - A-Z (Box 243, Folder 1-2)
      - Columbia University - Contributions (Box 243, Folder 3)
      - Columbia University - Printed Materials (Box 243, Folder 4)
      - Cornell University (Box 244, Folder 1)
      - Cornell University - Center for Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy (Box 244, Folder 2)
      - Cornell University - New York State College of Veterinary Medicine (Box 244, Folder 3, Box 245, Folder 1-3)
      - Cornell University - Printed Matter (Box 245, Folder 4)
      - Cumberland College (Box 245, Folder 5)
      - Dartmouth College - Alumni Fund (Box 245, Folder 6)
      - Dartmouth College - A-Z (Box 246, Folder 1)
      - Dartmouth College - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences, 1982-1986 (Box 246, Folder 2-3, Box 247, Folder 1)
      - Dartmouth College - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences - F-R (Box 247, Folder 2)
      - Dartmouth College - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences - Contributions, 1980-1982 (Box 247, Folder 3-4)
      - Dartmouth College - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences - Dedication (Box 248, Folder 1)
      - Dartmouth College - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences -Dedication - Invitations (Box 248, Folder 2)
      - Dartmouth College - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences - Printed Matter (Box 248, Folder 3)
      - Duke University (Box 249, Folder 1)
      - Emory University (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - Fisk University (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - Florida Memorial College, Miami, FL (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Fordham University (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - Georgetown University (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Georgetown University - Center for Strategic and International Studies (Box 250, Folder 4, Box 251, Folder 1)
      - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - Hahnemann University (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - Harvard University - A-M (Box 251, Folder 4-5)
      - Harvard University - N-Z (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - Harvard University - Black Rock Forest (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - Harvard University - Board of Overseers (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - Harvard University - Center for International Affairs (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - Harvard University - Contributions (Box 253, Folder 1)
      - Harvard University - Contributions - A-Z (Box 253, Folder 2-4)
      - Harvard University - Fund Raising (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Harvard University - Fund Raising - Core Fund Drive (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Harvard University - Fogg Art Museum (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - Harvard University - Graduate School of Education (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - Harvard University - Harvard College Fund (Box 254, Folder 5)
      - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - Harvard University - Harvard Law School (Box 255, Folder 2)
      - Harvard University - Harvard Medical School (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Harvard University - History of Science Society (Box 255, Folder 4)
      - Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1982-1986 (Box 256, Folder 1-3)
      - Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government - Contributions (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - Harvard University - Women, Religion, and Social Change (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Iona College (Box 257, Folder 2)
      - Johns Hopkins University (Box 257, Folder 3)
      - Macalester College (Box 257, Folder 4)
      - Manhattan College (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Marlboro College (Box 258, Folder 2)
      - Marlboro Music (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Marymount College, Tarrytown, NY (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Marymount College, New York, NY (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - A-Z (Box 259, Folder 2-3)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Endowed Professorships at MIT - A History, 1979-1982 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Contributions (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Corporation Members (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Minutes-Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 261, Folder 1-4)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Minutes-Meetings, 1984-1986 (Box 262, Folder 1-4)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Printed Matter (Box 263, Folder 1-2)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) -Report of the Treasurer, 1982-1986 (Box 263, Folder 3-4)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Reports to the President, 1983-1984 (Box 264, Folder 1)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Releases - Reports (Box 264, Folder 2)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Visiting Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 264, Folder 3)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Laurance S. Rockefeller Professorship in Philosophy (Box 264, Folder 4)
      - Middlebury College (Box 264, Folder 5)
      - New School for Social Research (Box 265, Folder 1)
      - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine (Box 265, Folder 2)
      - New York University (NYU) - A-Z (Box 265, Folder 3)
      - New York University (NYU) - Elmer Holmes Bobst Library and Study (Box 265, Folder 4)
      - New York University (NYU) - Center for War, Peace, and News Media (Box 266, Folder 1-2)
      - New York University (NYU) - Faculty of Arts and Science (Box 266, Folder 3)
      - New York University (NYU) - Graduate School of Business Administration (Box 266, Folder 4)
      - New York University (NYU) - Exploratory Project on the Conditions of Peace (Box 267, Folder 1)
      - New York University (NYU) - Medical Center (Box 267, Folder 2)
      - North Carolina State University (Box 267, Folder 3)
      - Northwood Institute (Box 267, Folder 4)
      - Princeton University - A-Z (Box 268, Folder 1-3)
      - Princeton University - Art Museum (Box 268, Folder 4)
      - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - A-Z (Box 268, Folder 5)
      - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies (Box 269, Folder 1-3, Box 270, Folder 1)
      - Princeton University - Contributions (Box 270, Folder 2)
      - Princeton University - Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 270, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University - Contributions - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Annual Giving and Class of 1932 (Box 271, Folder 1-2)
      - Princeton University - Finances (Box 271, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University - Forrestal Center (Box 271, Folder 4)
      - Princeton University - Fundraising - A Campaign for Princeton, 1978-1986 (Box 271, Folder 5, Box 272, Folder 1-3)
      - Princeton University - Fundraising - A Campaign for Princeton - A-Z (Box 272, Folder 4, Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Princeton University - Fundraising - A Campaign for Princeton - Campaign Bulletin (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Princeton University - Fundraising - A Campaign for Princeton - Camping Bulletin - Firestone (Box 273, Folder 3-4)
      - Princeton University - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Board of Trustees - Minutes-Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 274, Folder 1-3, Box 275, Folder 1)
      - Princeton University - Princeton Education Center at Blairstown (Box 275, Folder 2)
      - Princeton University - Printed Matter (Box 275, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University - Residential Colleges in Commons Area (Rockefeller College), 1980-1986 (Box 275, Folder 4, Box 276, Folder 1)
      - Princeton University - John D. Rockefeller 3rd College - Dedication (Box 276, Folder 2)
      - Princeton University - Residential Colleges in Common Area (John D. Rockefeller 3rd College on Holder Court) - Contributions - Rockefeller family (Box 276, Folder 3)
      - Princeton University - Rockefeller Public Service Awards (Box 276, Folder 4)
      - Princeton University - Lewis Thomas Laboratory (Molecular Biology Laboratory) (Box 277, Folder 1)
      - Radcliffe College (Box 277, Folder 2)
      - Rutgers, State University, New Brunswick, NJ (Box 277, Folder 3)
      - Smith College, Northampton, MA (Box 277, Folder 4)
      - Hobart and William Smith College (Box 278, Folder 1)
      - Spelman College (Box 278, Folder 2-3)
      - Stanford University (Box 278, Folder 4, Box 279, Folder 1)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) (Box 279, Folder 2-3)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) at Albany - Nelson A. Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government (Box 280, Folder 1-2)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) at Albany - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government - Dedication (Box 280, Folder 3)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) at Albany - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government - Publications (Box 280, Folder 4, Box 281, Folder 1-4)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) at Albany - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government - 1983-1984 New York Statistical Yearbook (Box 282, Folder 1)
      - State University of New York (SUNY) at Binghamton (Box 282, Folder 2)
      - Tufts University (Box 282, Folder 3, Box 283, Folder 1)
      - Union Theological Seminary (Box 283, Folder 2)
      - United Negro College Fund (Box 283, Folder 3)
      - United Negro College Fund - 39th Anniversary Dinner, 1983 March (Box 284, Folder 1)
      - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia (Box 284, Folder 2)
      - University of Arizona (Box 284, Folder 3)
      - University of Arkansas (Box 284, Folder 4)
      - University of Capetown (Box 284, Folder 5)
      - University of California (Box 285, Folder 1-2)
      - University of Chicago (Box 285, Folder 3-4)
      - University of Colorado (Box 286, Folder 1)
      - University of Dallas (Box 286, Folder 2)
      - University of Iowa (Box 286, Folder 3-4)
      - University of London - London School of Economics and Political Science (Box 286, Folder 5)
      - University of Maryland (Box 287, Folder 1)
      - University of Miami (Box 287, Folder 2)
      - University of Michigan (Box 287, Folder 3)
      - University of Minnesota (Box 287, Folder 4)
      - University of Northern Iowa (Box 287, Folder 5)
      - University of Notre Dame (Box 287, Folder 6)
      - University of Pennsylvania (Box 287, Folder 7)
      - University of Pittsburgh (Box 287, Folder 8)
      - University of Pennsylvania - School of Veterinary Medicine (Box 288, Folder 1)
      - University of Sussex (Box 288, Folder 2)
      - University of Texas (Box 288, Folder 3)
      - University of the Valley of Guatemala (Box 289, Folder 1)
      - University of Vermont (Box 289, Folder 2)
      - University of Vermont - Billings Library-Ira Allen Chapel (Box 289, Folder 3-4)
      - University of Virginia (Box 290, Folder 1)
      - University of Waterloo (Box 290, Folder 2)
      - University of Wyoming (Box 290, Folder 3)
      - Vassar College (Box 290, Folder 4)
      - Vermont Law School (Box 290, Folder 5)
      - Wellesly College, Boston, MA (Box 290, Folder 6)
      - World College West (Box 290, Folder 7, Box 291, Folder 1)
      - Yale University, 1981-1986 (Box 291, Folder 2-3)
      - Yale University - Printed Material (Box 291, Folder 4)
      - Yeshiva University (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Students Service, 3
      - Foreign Students Service (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Foundations, 4
      - Foundations - A-B (Box 292, Folder 3-4)
      - Foundations - B-H (Box 293, Folder 1-4)
      - Foundations - I-M (Box 294, Folder 1-3)
      - Foundations - N-Z (Box 295, Folder 1-3)
      - Capp Street Foundation (Box 296, Folder 1-2)
      - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, Inc. (Box 296, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Free Expression (Box 296, Folder 4)
      - Fundacion Luis Munoz Marin (Box 297, Folder 1)
      - The Funding Exchange (Box 297, Folder 2)
      - High Winds Fund (Box 297, Folder 3, Box 298, Folder 1)
      - L.A.W. Fund (Box 298, Folder 2)
      - L.A.W. Fund - Meetings (Box 298, Folder 3)
      - Lakeview Fund, Inc. (Box 298, Folder 4)
      - George C. Marshall Research Foundation (Box 299, Folder 1)
      - The Rand Corporation (Box 299, Folder 2)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - A-Z (Box 299, Folder 3)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Board of Trustees (Box 299, Folder 4)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Finances (Box 300, Folder 1)
      - DeWitt Wallace Fund, Inc. (Box 300, Folder 2-3)
      - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation (WWNFF) (Box 300, Folder 4, Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Historical Societies, 5
      - Historical Societies - A-Z (Box 301, Folder 2-3)
      - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns (Box 301, Folder 4)
      - Mystic Seaport Museum (Box 302, Folder 1)
      - National Maritime Historical Society (Box 302, Folder 2)
      - New York Historical Society (Box 302, Folder 3)
      - The Newcomen Society in the U.S. (Box 302, Folder 4)
      - Rhode Island Historical Society (Box 302, Folder 5)
      - Royal Oak Foundation (Box 302, Folder 6)
      - Woodstock Historical Society (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - Housing, 6
      - International Houses (Box 303, Folder 2)
      - International House, Chicago (Box 303, Folder 3)
      - International House - Board of Trustees (Box 303, Folder 4)
      - International House, New York (Box 303, Folder 5, Box 304, Folder 1)
      - International House, New York - Contributions (Box 304, Folder 2)
      - International House, New York - Fund Raising (Box 304, Folder 3)
      - International House - Minutes-Meetings (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Radio/Television, 7
      - Radio-Television - A-B (Box 304, Folder 5-6)
      - Radio-Television - C-S (Box 305, Folder 1-4)
      - Radio-Television - T-Z (Box 306, Folder 1-2)
      - Action for Children's Television (Box 306, Folder 3)
      - Center for Communication (Box 307, Folder 1)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - General (Box 307, Folder 2-3)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - A-Z (Box 307, Folder 4)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Alice in Wonderland (Box 308, Folder 1)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Contributions (Box 308, Folder 2-3)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Laurance S. Rockefeller Contributions (Box 309, Folder 1)
      - Greater Washington Educational Telecommunications Association (Box 309, Folder 2)
      - Listeners Community Radio of Utah, Inc. (Box 309, Folder 3)
      - Press and Public Project, Inc. (Box 309, Folder 4)
      - Martha Stuart Communications, Inc. (Box 309, Folder 5)
      - Twin Cities Public Television (Box 310, Folder 1)
      - WGBH (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Schools, 8
      - Schools - A-B (Box 310, Folder 3-4)
      - Schools - B-G (Box 311, Folder 1-4)
      - Schools - H-M (Box 312, Folder 1-3)
      - Schools - N-P (Box 313, Folder 1-3)
      - Schools - Q-Z (Box 314, Folder 1-2)
      - Brearley School (Box 314, Folder 3)
      - The Buckley School in New York (Box 315, Folder 1)
      - Chapin School (Box 315, Folder 2)
      - Choate Rosemary Hall (Box 315, Folder 3)
      - Churchill School and Center for Learning Disabilities in New York, NY (Box 315, Folder 4)
      - Deerfield Academy (Box 315, Folder 5)
      - Good Hope School (Box 316, Folder 1)
      - Hurricane Island Outward Bound School (Box 316, Folder 2)
      - Kildonan School (Box 316, Folder 3)
      - The Lab School of Washington, Washington, DC (Box 316, Folder 4)
      - Madeira School (Box 317, Folder 1)
      - Mannes College of Music (Box 317, Folder 2)
      - Midwest Academy (Box 317, Folder 3)
      - Miss Porter's School (Box 317, Folder 4)
      - Navajo Pine High School (Box 318, Folder 1)
      - New York City School Volunteer Program, Inc. (Box 318, Folder 2)
      - New York Studio School of Drawing, Painting, and Sculpture (Box 318, Folder 3)
      - North Carolina Outward Bound School (Box 318, Folder 4)
      - North Country School (Box 318, Folder 5)
      - Phillips Academy, Andover, MA (Box 318, Folder 6)
      - Phillips Exeter Academy (Box 318, Folder 7)
      - Pocantico Hills Central School District (Box 319, Folder 1)
      - Professional Children's School (Box 319, Folder 2)
      - Reading is Fundamental (Box 319, Folder 3)
      - The Shipley School (Box 319, Folder 4)
      - Shady Hill School (Box 319, Folder 5)
      - School for Field Studies (Box 320, Folder 1)
      - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture (Box 320, Folder 2-3)
      - United World Colleges, Inc. (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Energy, 1982-1986; 13; 5.03 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
    - Energy - A-B (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Energy - C-G (Box 321, Folder 1-4)
    - Energy - H-P (Box 322, Folder 1-5)
    - Energy - P-Z (Box 323, Folder 1-4)
    - Center for Renewable Resources (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Center for Renewable Resources - Printed Material (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Citizen's Clearinghouse for Hazardous Wastes (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Clinch River Breeder Reactor (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Community Energy Ventures (Box 325, Folder 2-3)
    - Energy Conservation Coalition (Box 326, Folder 1-3)
    - Energy Research Foundation (Box 326, Folder 4, Box 327, Folder 1-2)
    - Energy Systems Research Group, Inc. (Box 327, Folder 3-4)
    - The Fund for Secure Energy, Inc. (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Health and Energy Institute (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Ladakh Solar Project (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - National Public Power Institute (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - New Hampshire Energy Coalition (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - New Renaissance Center (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Nuclear Information and Resource Service (Box 329, Folder 1-3, Box 330, Folder 1-4)
    - People Against Nuclear Energy (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Rulemaking Project (Box 331, Folder 2-3)
    - Safe Energy Communications Council (SECC) (Box 331, Folder 4, Box 332, Folder 1)
    - World Information Service on Energy (WISE) (Box 332, Folder 2)
  - F-I, 1982-1986; 14; 1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
    - F - Miscellaneous (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - G - Miscellaneous (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Geriatrics (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Geriatrics - National Council on the Aging (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - H - Miscellaneous (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Hispanic Affairs - A-Z (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Hispanic Affairs - Casita Maria (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Horticulture - A-Z (Box 334, Folder 2-5)
    - Horticulture - Brooklyn Botanical Garden (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Horticulture - Landscape Architecture Foundation (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Horticulture - New York Botanical Garden (Box 335, Folder 3-5)
    - Horticulture - New York Botanical Garden - Printed Material (Box 336, Folder 1-2)
    - Horticulture - Pacific Tropical Botanical Garden (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) (Box 336, Folder 4)
  - International Relations, 1982-1986; 15; 41.49 Cubic Feet 107 letter document boxes, 2 half-letter document boxes and 1 legal box
    - International Relations - A-Z, 1
      - International Relations - A (Box 336, Folder 5)
      - International Relations - A-H (Box 337, Folder 1-4)
      - International Relations - I-O (Box 338, Folder 1-4)
      - International Relations - P-Z (Box 339, Folder 1-2)
      - American Austrian Foundation (Box 339, Folder 4)
      - Amnesty International of the USA (Box 340, Folder 1)
      - Atlantic Council of the United States (Box 340, Folder 2)
      - Children's Art Exchange (Box 340, Folder 3)
      - The English Speaking Union (Box 340, Folder 4)
      - The Foundation for International Conciliation (Box 340, Folder 5)
      - Institute for East-West Security Studies (Box 341, Folder 1-2)
      - Institute for Soviet-American Relations (Box 341, Folder 3-4)
      - Interaction Council of Former Heads of Government (Box 342, Folder 1)
      - Interlink Press Service (Box 342, Folder 2)
      - International Institute for Environment and Development (Box 342, Folder 3-4)
      - International Institute for Strategic Studies (Box 342, Folder 5)
      - International Institute of Geopolitics (Box 343, Folder 1)
      - International League for Human Rights (Box 343, Folder 2)
      - International Rescue Committee, Inc. (Box 343, Folder 3)
      - Roosevelt Center for American Policy Studies (Box 343, Folder 5, Box 344, Folder 1)
      - Spanish Institute (Box 344, Folder 2)
      - Americanism (Box 347, Folder 1)
      - World Affairs Council of Inland Southern California (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - Countries/Continents, 2
      - Afghanistan - A-Z (Box 339, Folder 3)
      - Africa - A-L (Box 344, Folder 3)
      - Africa - M-Z (Box 345, Folder 1)
      - Africa - African-American Institute (Box 345, Folder 2-3)
      - Africa - Africare (Box 345, Folder 4)
      - Africa - Morroccan-American Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 346, Folder 1-2)
      - Africa - Partnership for African Development (Box 346, Folder 3)
      - Africa - South Africa (Box 346, Folder 4)
      - Asia - A-Z (Box 347, Folder 3)
      - Asia - Agriculture Development Council, Inc. (Box 347, Folder 4)
      - Asia - Asia Society - A-Z, 1978-1985 (Box 347, Folder 5-6)
      - Asia - Asia Society, 1978-1984 (Box 348, Folder 1)
      - Asia - Asia Society - Annual Dinner 1985 (Box 348, Folder 2)
      - Asia - Asia Society - Board of Trustees (Box 348, Folder 3)
      - Asia - Asia Society - Contributions (Box 348, Folder 4)
      - Asia - Asia Society - Fundraising (Box 348, Folder 5)
      - Asia - Asian Cultural Council (Box 348, Folder 6)
      - Asia - East West Center Foundation (Box 349, Folder 1)
      - Asia - East West Center Foundation - Printed Matter (Box 349, Folder 2-3)
      - Australia (Box 349, Folder 4)
      - Canada (Box 350, Folder 1)
      - China (Box 350, Folder 2-3)
      - China - National Committee on United States-China Relations (Box 350, Folder 4)
      - Costa Rica (Box 350, Folder 5)